A Guide to the Records of the Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind at Hampton, xxxx-xxxx
Library of Virginia
- Series IV. Committee and Council records, xxxx-xxxx., Extent: xx cu. ft. (x boxes) (Box 23-)
  - Ad Hoc Program Task Force, 1990 July 27. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1980 Mar-Dec. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1981. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1982 Jan-June. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1992 Aug-Dec. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1983 Jan-Mar. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1983 Apr-June. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1983 Aug-Sept. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1983 Oct-Dec. (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1983. (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1984 Jan-Mar. (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1984 Apr-June. (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1984 July-Sept. (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1984 Oct-Dec. (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1985 Jan-Mar. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1985 Apr-June. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1985 July-Sept. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1985 Oct-Dec. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1986 Jan-Mar. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1986 Apr-June. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1986 July-Sept. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1986 Oct-Dec. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1987 Jan-Mar. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1987 Apr-June. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1987 July-Sept. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1987 Oct-Dec. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1988 Jan-Mar. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1988 Apr-June. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1988 July-Sept. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1988 Oct-Dec. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1989 Jan-Mar. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Administrative Council - Minutes and Agendas, 1989 Apr-June. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Advisory Committee - Minutes and Agendas, 1985 Nov. (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Advisory Committee - Minutes and Agendas, 1985 Dec. (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Advisory Committee - Minutes and Agendas, 1986 Jan. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Committee - Minutes and Agendas, 1986 Mar. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Advisory Committee - Minutes and Agendas, 1990 May. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Advisory Committee - Minutes and Agendas, 1990 Sept. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Advisory Committee - Minutes and Agendas, 1990 Dec. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Advisory Committee - Minutes and Agendas, 1991 May. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Advisory Commission - Minutes and Agendas, 2001 Oct. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Advisory Commission - Minutes and Agendas, 2007 June. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Advisory Commission - Minutes and Agendas, 2007 Sept. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Advisory Commission - Minutes and Agendas, 2007 Dec. (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Communication Review Committee (Sign Language), 1987. (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Manual Communication Committee (Sign Language), 1979-1980. (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Manual Communication Committee (Sign Language), 1981-1982. (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Manual Communication Committee (Sign Language), 1984. (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Manual Communication Committee (Sign Language), 1986. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Manual Communication Committee (Sign Language), 1987. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Program Support Committee, 1992-1996. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Program Support Committee - Meeting, 1995 Nov. (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Series V. Foundation, Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind, xxxx-xxxx., Extent: .2 cu. ft. (1 box) (Box 27)
  Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind Foundation records, xx-xx, are housed in 1 box and arranged chronologically.
  - General records, 1993-1996. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - General records, 2001-2006. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Annual Board meeting, 1982. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Annual Board meeting, 1992. (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Annual Board meeting, 1996. (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Annual Board meeting, 1997. (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Annual Board meeting, 2001. (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Annual Board meeting, 2002. (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Annual Board meeting, 2003. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Annual Board meeting, 2004. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Annual Board meeting, 2005. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Annual Board meeting, 2008. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Series VI. Newsletters, 1981-2008., Extent: .35 cu. ft. (1 box) (Box 28)
  Newsletters, 1981-2008, are housed in 1 box and arranged alphabetically by title.
  - D and T News Express, 2000 Apr, June. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Eagle Extra - Student Life Newsletter, 1994 Oct-Dec. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Eagle News, 2004 Jan. (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Eagle Watch, 1981 Sept. (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Eagle Watch, 1987 Sept-Dec. (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Eagle Watch, 1988 Jan-Apr. (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Eagle Watch, 2008 Apr-June. (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Eagle's Nes, 1992 Sept. (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - HR News, 1999 July/Aug. (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - The Personnel Touch, 1999 Sept-Dec. (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - The Personnel Touch, 2002-2003. (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - VSDBH Parent Newsletter, 1992-2993. (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - VSDBH Parent Newsletter, 1995. (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Virginia School News, 1995 Dec. (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Virginia School News, 1996 Jan. (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Virginia School News, 1996 May. (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Virginia School News, 1996 Fall. (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Virginia School News, 1997 Spring/Fall/Winter. (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Virginia School News, 1998 Spring. (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Virginia School News, 1998 Winter. (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Virginia School News, 1999 Spring/Summer. (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Virginia School News, 1999 Winter. (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Virginia School News, 1999-2000. (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Virginia School News, 2000 Fall. (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Other states: Deleware, 19. (Box 28, Folder 29)
- Series VII. Yearbooks, 1982-2001., Extent: .25 cu. ft. (1 box) (Box 29)
  Yearbooks, 1982-2003, are housed in 1 box and arranged chronologically. This is not a complete series and only includes 5 yearbooks: 1982-1983; 1992; 1999-2000; 2000-2001 and 2003. Yearbook, 2003, is in Braille.
  - Yearbook, 1982-1983. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Yearbook, 1992. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Yearbook, 1999-2000. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Yearbook, 2000-2001. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Yearbook (Braille), 2003. (Box 32, Folder 1)